Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
HAVANA. CUBA
We swap in parts from Ford
Plymouths and Cadillac.
My grandfather bought it in 1957.
When he died it passed to my father.
Then my brother and now to me.
Look at this.
this is an engine from a boat.
- No way.
- Yeah!
Whatever it takes to keep it running!
This is a cuban spirit.
Your spirit. keep it up.
Never ever lose that.
Dom..
It's your cousin..
He's in trouble. come quickly!
Come on. come on.
Please don't do this.
Understand my problem.
You should show your
people some respect.
I am really scared.
Are you ready for this. family?
This is Havana!
Be fast!
Be safe!
But don't be last.
Racers ready...?
Go...!
Stop.
Can I help you with that?
Look out...!
Chick..
Hobbs!
We land back in Moscow by nine.
Here's the latest defense report.
All the items in yesterday's meet.
AUTO-DRIVE ACTIVATED.
Hey...!
What is going on?
Drive fast!
Drive! Drive!
There's more cars ahead of us.
Shoot their engines.
Oh God!
We got an army of cars
driving themselves.
Send backup! Send S.W.A.T!
I don't care if you send the
goddamn boy scout...
- Just send up some help!
- Now that's Dom.
Faster. faster!
The motorcade just turned on 7th.
Perfect. Make it rain.
Target immobilized.
You are up Dom.
- Who the hell is that?
- What is he doing?
What the hell
are you waiting for?
Shoot him!
Come on. come on!
I'm out.
Shit.
Don't worry sir.
This car is bulletproof.
You'll be safe in here.
- Give me the case.
- Give him the case.
These are nuclear launch codes.
We cannot give it to him.
What is he doing now?
He just cut a hole
in our gas tank.
- Look out!
- Wait. wait. wait!
See you later...
We have a possible
threat incoming.
Raise the barricade.
As soon as possible.
We've lost power.
get to your positions now.
Engaging target.
He's beneath the Sub.
I'm loosing control. mayday. mayday.
I'm going down.
You're driving.
I said it from the beginning.
No way. I'm not driving.
Thank you for giving us family.
Thank you for giving us the strength.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm